Yesterday afternoon Frank Hawkins was telling me about his experiences as a young man.
Before he retired, Frank was the head of a very large business company, but as a boy he used to work in a small shop.
It was his job to repair bicycles and at that time he used to work fourteen hours a day.
He saved money for years and in 1958 he bought a small workshop of his own.
In his twenties Frank used to make spare parts for aeroplanes.
At that time he had two helpers.
In a few years the small workshop had become a large factory which employed seven hundred and twenty-eight people.
Frank smiled when he remembered his hard early years and the long road to success.
He was still smiling when the door opened and his wife came in.
She wanted him to repair their grandson's bicycle!